[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[elevator bell dings]
[speaking Japanese]
[person shouts]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
Aah!
- [speaking Japanese]
[TV clicks off]
I came off like an asshole.
No, you sounded thoughtful
and looked very, very handsome.
Your friends are very cute.
- Oh, I know.
I tell them all the time.
- [giggles]
Uh...
It's just my friend Samantha.
Mm.
St. Louis?
Yeah.
It's to go home
for my dad's 60th birthday.
And the "Meicho" will let
their star reporter
have time off?
Hmm?
Do you not want to go?
No, it's just kind of...
complicated with my family.
Plus, I'd rather stay here
with you.
[speaking Japanese]
Wait to go out.
Our rendezvous spot?
That's not going out.
Aren't you tired
of sneaking over here
and never leaving this room?
Jake...
You know it's too dangerous.
- I'm tired of hiding.
- I am, too.
But we have to be patient
and careful.
Because I'm really good
at being patient and careful.
[both laughing]
[speaking Japanese]
[knock at door]
[door opens]
[speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
- Hai.
[speaking Japanese]
[door opens]
[door closes]
- [speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
[both groaning]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[speaking Japanese]
[cell phone vibrating]
[cell phone beeps]
Hai.
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[upbeat dance music playing]
♪ ♪
Why don't you let
me cook for you?
Come to my house.
I'll make you a meal.
- You want to make me a meal?
- Yes, I do.
How nice of you, Ohno-san.
[speaking Japanese]
So what do you say?
I'm flattered.
Which usually means no.
It's just that I have rules.
Samantha...
I feel we made a real
connection these last weeks.
I'd like to see where it goes,
if you're willing.
Let me think about it.
Sure.
[clatter, laughter]
[speaking Japanese]
[softly]
Erika.
- I'll just be a minute.
- Sure.
Good evening, Ohno-san.
[speaking Japanese]
Are you going to do
something about this?
There's nothing I can do.
Hmm.
[speaking Japanese]
♪ ♪
[Erika speaking Japanese]
[stomach rumbling]
[laughing]
[speaking Japanese]
[stomach rumbles, both chuckle]
[door opens, closes]
[speaking Japanese]
[chuckles]
Hmm.
[Erika chuckles]
[door closes]
[both laughing]
[speaking Japanese]
Last night was
the third time this month
that he's been in my club.
He's chasing my clients away.
Who the fuck is he?
Hayama.
He's the wakagashira
of Chihara-kai--
Ishida's number two.
Sato's supposed to
look after my club.
Last night, he just sat there.
He wouldn't lift
a finger to help me.
Yeah, well, there's
not much he can do
because Hayama outranks him.
Will you talk to him for me,
see if he can do something?
To Sato?
Uh...
[chuckles]
The last time I saw Sato,
I got kicked out of Onyx
for trying to fight him.
So we stay clear of each other.
Why don't you talk to him?
I thought you guys
were, like...
Not anymore.
Business and pleasure--
not a great mix.
Yeah, I hear that.
Are you seeing someone?
Yeah.
For a while now.
It's really good.
I mean, it's complicated,
but it's good.
Look at you, all grown up.
Well, let's not go that far.
[groans] I can't have
this guy in my club.
Go to Sato as a friend...
and ask for his help.
[sighs]
[speaking Japanese]
Yeah!
Two articles about motorcycle
thieves, and now you're a hero.
Don't do that.
Cynicism is lazy.
I agree.
It's our mission
to try and change things.
Yes, try and change things.
But why do Americans
think it's your job
to fix the entire world?
- Well, someone's got to do it.
- Mm.
I have to get back to work.
But take these.
Invitations
to an official function
at the U.S. ambassador's
residence tomorrow night.
You're all going
to cultivate sources.
[speaking Japanese]
[speaking Korean]
[door closes]
[light classical music
playing]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
I thought we were meeting
here next week.
This couldn't wait.
[gasps]
Is this a plane ticket
to Missouri?
No, it's better.
It's an invitation
to a U.S. embassy party...
tomorrow night.
You're going to be my plus-one.
Shh.
[whispering]
Invent a name for you
and get you on the list.
[whispering]
Jake...
it's still such a risk.
It's just one night...
you and me on a real date.
It's perfect.
♪ ♪
[muffled rap music thumping]
[singing in Korean]
♪ ♪
[door closes]
[speaking Korean]
[music volume decreases]
[volume increases]
[singing along]
♪ ♪
♪ Everybody ♪
[crowd shouts]
♪ Rock your body ♪
♪ Everybody ♪
♪ Rock your body right ♪
[cheers]
♪ Backstreet's back,
all right ♪
[speaking Japanese]
Whoo!
Yeah, yeah!
♪ Brothers, sisters,
everybody sing ♪
- [speaking Japanese]
[speaking Japanese]
[all shouting]
all:
♪ Everybody, yeah ♪
♪ Rock your body, yeah ♪
[laughs]
♪ Am I the only one? ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Am I sexual? ♪
♪ Am I everything you need?
You better rock your body now ♪
♪ Everybody,
rock your body right ♪
[engine revving]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
Hey.
I just left you a message
about meeting up.
I was already on my way here.
I need to talk to you, too.
Okay.
[sighs]
We have a problem.
- You mean about Hayama?
- Mm-hmm.
Will you talk to Ishida?
Make him understand
Hayama's bad for business.
The Oyabun will keep
him out of the club
after you do something for him.
The architect.
Ohno-san?
What about him?
He works for the city--
chief designer
of a new shopping center
to be built
on a railway station.
The Oyabun wants to know which
station before it's public...
to buy all the surrounding land
before the announcement
makes it prime real estate.
I'm not spying
on a customer for you.
The success of my place
depends on discretion.
For Oyabun,
knowing which railway station
is more valuable than the club.
And the club belongs to him.
So now you're threatening me?
I told you not
to fire Claudine.
She was fucking
stealing from me.
She was working for us.
[grunts]
She was sitting
with the architect every night,
getting information.
But now all he wants is you.
So you must finish the job.
And if I say no?
Please, trust me...
do not say no.
I'm sorry.
I need your answer tomorrow.
[speaking Japanese]
[person speaking Japanese]
[sighs sharply]
[knocking at door]
[knocking continues]
[shouts]
Uh...
[speaking Japanese]
Uh-huh.
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
[gun cocks]
[gun clatters]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
[applause]
[cell phone beeps]
[line trilling]
[Natsumi speaking Japanese
over phone]
[chuckles]
- Mm, bye-bye.
[cell phone beeps,
distant chatter and laughter]
all:
♪ In daylights, in sunsets ♪
♪ In midnights,
in cups of coffee ♪
♪ In inches, in miles,
in laughter, in strife. ♪
♪ How about love? ♪
all:
♪ Seasons of love, love. ♪
Here we go.
[applause]
Thank you to the cast members
of "Rent."
So please say hi to them
as you enjoy something to eat.
[Makoto speaking Japanese]
[elegant music playing]
Lynn is in the FBI,
so she only deals
with federal crimes.
Well, at least American law
acknowledges the problem.
Women in the U.S.
can take out restraining orders
against their stalkers.
Yes, that's true,
but we could be a lot more
effective with prevention.
If you'd like, I could get you
the latest American statistics.
I would.
Can we talk on Monday?
- Absolutely.
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
Yes, I had the shrimp puffs.
They were delicious.
- [chuckles]
Jason Aoki, U.S. Embassy.
Jun Shinohara,
"Meicho Shimbun."
A journalist?
[laughs]
I was wrong.
My colleagues and I play a game
where we try to guess what
people do before we meet them.
- What were the guesses?
- One did guess journalist.
One bet
retired baseball player.
[chuckles]
And I just lost money
betting you're a model.
You should meet another
of my reporters.
Jake Adelstein,
this is Lynn Oberfeld,
legal attaché at the embassy.
I've really enjoyed
reading your work.
When Hal Lieberman first said
there was an American
working on the "Meicho,"
I thought he was kidding.
- We are slowly civilizing him.
This is Jason Aoki
from my office.
- Nice to meet you.
- And you.
This is my friend Mari.
- Ah, journalist also?
- No.
I'm a choreographer--
modern dance.
Oh, forgive me.
I see a colleague
from the Korean embassy
who's been trying to get me
for weeks.
I'm sure we'll talk again.
Enjoy your evening.
You too.
I'm going to try
a shrimp puff.
I hear good things.
Modern dance?
You have no idea
how talented I am.
[both laugh]
[both chuckle]
- Ah...
[knock at door]
[door closes]
[chuckles]
[elegant music playing]
♪ ♪
Excuse me. Are you
the famous choreographer?
[chuckles]
Yes, I am.
And you choreographed
tonight's show?
Yes, I did.
Wasn't it great?
We're touring the world.
Our next stop is Missouri.
[both laugh]
Come with me.
Meet my family.
I-I know we've only been
together for a month,
and the very idea of us
being together is crazy,
but...
I want to believe that we have
a future together.
♪ ♪
What?
Did he see me?
Who?
That man.
I've see him with Tozawa.
Don't worry.
Nobody here has
any connection to Tozawa.
I have to go.
Hey, slow down.
Do not touch me.
Stay away from me.
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
You seem preoccupied?
Do I?
Not at all.
Are you concerned
about my proposal
that we spend time together
outside of here?
I'm still thinking about it.
I just need you to be patient.
Take all the time you need.
Can you excuse me
for a minute?
Sure.
God damn it.
- Sam?
- Yeah?
You deal with him.
I'll deal with them, okay?
- Okay.
- Divide and conquer.
Thank you.
[footsteps approaching]
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[can opens]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[clears throat]
Ahh.
♪ ♪
[banging on door]
[speaking Japanese]
[banging continues]
If the newspaper
speaks up for him,
we could get him
in reform school.
It doesn't matter
that he's a juvenile.
He was arrested while stealing
a motorcycle,
and he hit a policeman.
Reform school is off the table.
Maruyama-san, he's been
in a holding cell for a day.
The other prisoners
have already beat him up.
It will get worse
when he is transferred.
Juvenile prison here can be
even worse than adult ones.
Jesus.
[sighs]
Yo.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [grunts, speaks Japanese]
- [chuckles]
I'm busy, "Meicho"-san.
Listen...
the last time I saw you
at Onyx...
Oh.
I was out of line.
You tried to help me,
and I jumped to conclusions.
I heard you got beat up.
Yeah.
I heard you got stabbed.
[car door closes,
engine turning over]
[upbeat pop music playing]
[person speaking Japanese]
[speaking Japanese]
[speaks Japanese]
[slurps]
Which prison is he going to?
Probably Asaka in Saitama.
Guards there like to turn
the fire hoses on prisoners.
Um, one boy...
um...
[clears throat]
[lighter clinks]
I'll take care of it.
Take care of it, like...?
Make sure
he is protected inside
and give him a place with us
when he's out.
Eh?
- Mm...
Uh...
[sighs]
And you are paying
for dinner.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Maybe you should have skipped
the Kobe beef, huh?
[exhales sharply]
[laughing]
[distant indistinct chatter]
Aren't you all
going out for afters?
We are--
here, with you.
Sit with us.
Minami got some food.
[laughter]
- Kanpai.
[indistinct chatter]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
[speaking Japanese]
Huh?